<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>WICCA</title>
    <link>https://womenofwicca.nl/</link>
    <description>Recent content on WICCA</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 07 Apr 2020 18:00:00 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://womenofwicca.nl/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Xebia</title>
      <link>https://womenofwicca.nl/events/xebia/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Apr 2020 18:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://womenofwicca.nl/events/xebia/</guid>
      <description>Tue, Apr 7, 6:00 PM to 9:00 PM Location: Amsterdam
This meetup is organised by Xebia.
Stay tuned.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hardware Hacking 101 @Zerocopter</title>
      <link>https://womenofwicca.nl/events/hardware-hacking-101/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Mar 2020 18:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://womenofwicca.nl/events/hardware-hacking-101/</guid>
      <description>Thu, Mar 26, 6:00 PM to 9:00 PM Location: Amsterdam
Stay tuned.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Secura</title>
      <link>https://womenofwicca.nl/events/secura/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2020 18:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://womenofwicca.nl/events/secura/</guid>
      <description>Wed, Feb 26, 6:00 PM to 9:00 PM Location: Amsterdam
This meetup is organised by Secura.
Stay tuned.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Digital Crime Scene Investigations</title>
      <link>https://womenofwicca.nl/events/nfi/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2020 18:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://womenofwicca.nl/events/nfi/</guid>
      <description>Tue, Jan 28, 6:00 PM to 9:00 PM Location: Nederlands Forensisch Instituut
Ever wondered what the life of a digital crime scene investigator looks like? Step into the world of the NFI this evening and experience a live criminal case where your digital forensics skills will be required!
This meetup is organised by the Dutch Forensics Institute.
This event is women-only.
Curious what it&amp;rsquo;s like to work at NFI? You will hear experience from two kick-ass ladies!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hack The Box NL</title>
      <link>https://womenofwicca.nl/archive/htb-nl-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 18:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://womenofwicca.nl/archive/htb-nl-1/</guid>
      <description>Mon, Dec 09, 6:00 PM to 9:00 PM Location: KPN Teleport
Hack The Box, the popular online platform to test and advance penetration testing skills, has partnered up with the WICCA team to organise meetups in the Netherlands, where everyone can go crazy inside a HTB lab and hack the planet!!!!!!1!
EVERYONE is welcome to join the HTB Meetup group, and especially WICCA members!
To participate to this hacking adventure, register to the HTB NL group above and sign up for our first event on December 9.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ING: Hacking a Bank</title>
      <link>https://womenofwicca.nl/archive/ing-ctf/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2019 18:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://womenofwicca.nl/archive/ing-ctf/</guid>
      <description>Wed, Nov 27, 6:00 PM to 9:00 PM Location: ING HUB
HUB consists of 3 buildings: A, B and C. ING will organise this at the ground floor of the C-building, which is the long building facing Hotel Levell.
ING is inviting WICCA to their awesome open-for-all CTF!
Bring a laptop with Internet access!
How to teach anyone to be a hacker
Normally, Capture the Flag (CTF) events are organised for security enthusiasts only.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fox-IT</title>
      <link>https://womenofwicca.nl/archive/fox-it/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2019 18:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://womenofwicca.nl/archive/fox-it/</guid>
      <description>Wed, Oct 23, 6:00 PM to 9:00 PM Location: Fox-IT, Delft
Fox-IT, one of the top Dutch security companies, is inviting the ladies of InfoSec and female security enthusiasts in The Netherlands for an evening about Red &amp;amp; Blue Teaming in Delft. They will be hosting us at their office in Delft and is providing drinks and food.
Are you team red or team blue? Next to the Pokemon red and blue video games, we know two important teams in cyber security.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WICCA Goes Hardwear!</title>
      <link>https://womenofwicca.nl/archive/wicca-goes-hardwear/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2019 18:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://womenofwicca.nl/archive/wicca-goes-hardwear/</guid>
      <description>Wed, Sep 25, 6:00 PM to 9:00 PM Location: Hotel NH Den Haag
Great news!!! The organisers of hardwear.io have invited us to their after-training reception for a great networking opportunity!
Hardwear.io is the biggest hardware security conference in Europe, and possibly in the world. It is a platform where researchers showcase and discuss their innovative research on attacking and defending hardware.
https://hardwear.io/netherlands-2019/
This event takes place during the hardwear.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dutch Police: Fighting Cybercrime with OSINT</title>
      <link>https://womenofwicca.nl/archive/dutch-police/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Sep 2019 18:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://womenofwicca.nl/archive/dutch-police/</guid>
      <description>Mon, Sep 23, 6:00 PM to 9:00 PM Location: Deloitte Amsterdam
WICCA is going awol to a session organised together with the Dutch Police.
This session is WOMEN-ONLY.
Deloitte will be hosting us all with food and drinks.
Would you like to know more about Open Source Intelligence (OSINT)? Have you ever wondered what it is like to work at the Dutch Police? Join us for the upcoming OSINT session with Lisette Abercrombie and Maike Borst!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Secure Coding (... or the Art of Avoiding Data Breaches)</title>
      <link>https://womenofwicca.nl/archive/secure-coding/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2019 18:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://womenofwicca.nl/archive/secure-coding/</guid>
      <description>Fri, Aug 30, 6:00 PM to 10:00 PM Location: Saturnusstraat 14
WICCA is coming to The Hague for a session on secure coding and privacy-oriented software engineering. This session is organised together with Okuna and will cover the following topics: secure coding, privacy preservation, security and development.
Okuna (previously Openbook) embodies the future of social media: a privacy-oriented and transparent platform that is secure by design, which strives for a better tomorrow for our online social circles.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wick-Ed Offensive Security</title>
      <link>https://womenofwicca.nl/archive/wick-ed-offensive-security/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2019 18:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://womenofwicca.nl/archive/wick-ed-offensive-security/</guid>
      <description>Slides can be found here Lesson recording on YouTube Mon, Jul 29, 6:00 PM to 9:00 PM Location: KPN Teleport
WICCA kicks off a new initiative to teach ladies about security: Wick-Ed!
Because of the high Offensive Security training demand, we will be doing the first Wick-Ed session on Offensive Security on July 29. KPN will be hosting us again and is providing food and drinks. For anyone who could not attend the 2-day training on May 25-26, this is the occasion to pick up on the basics of offsec!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WICCA Drinks&amp;Stories</title>
      <link>https://womenofwicca.nl/archive/drinks-stories-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2019 10:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://womenofwicca.nl/archive/drinks-stories-2/</guid>
      <description>Thu, Jun 20, 8:00 PM to 10:00 PM Location: Pllek
WICCA is breaking into Amsterdam for some drinks and hacker stories. Are you a woman working or interested in computer security? Join us for some goofy hacker fun! Male +1s are welcome.
The event will start 20:00 and the place to be is: Pllek, which is reachable by (free) ferry from Amsterdam Centraal station.
Just a heads-up, every one should take care of their own consumption, as this is just a get-together event among fellow willing WICCA ladies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Offensive Security 101</title>
      <link>https://womenofwicca.nl/archive/offensive-security-101/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 May 2019 10:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://womenofwicca.nl/archive/offensive-security-101/</guid>
      <description>Training slides can be found here Sat, May 25, 10:00 AM to Sun, May 26, 5:00 PM Location: Securify
WICCA is giving a two-day training in Offensive Security especially for beginners. Securify is hosting us in their Sloterdijk office and will be providing lunch and Club Mate!
The training will include:
 Basic infrastructure and web introduction Network vulnerability scanning Offensive Security tooling Web application pwnage OWASP Top 10 Kernel exploits A tiny bit about malware reversing A Hackback CTF-like game Demos and more demos!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kubernetes with WICCA &amp; null Amsterdam @Adyen</title>
      <link>https://womenofwicca.nl/archive/kubernetes-wicca-null-adyen/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2019 18:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://womenofwicca.nl/archive/kubernetes-wicca-null-adyen/</guid>
      <description>Mon, May 13, 6:00 PM to 9:30 PM Location: Adyen
This evening session is a joint meetup between WICCA and null hosted by Adyen, where members from both communities are happily invited to attend. Adyen is a global payment service provider based in Amsterdam. They will be providing food and drinks for all of us!!! 😄
null is India&amp;rsquo;s largest open security community with chapters all over the world, including Amsterdam.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hacking Hoomans</title>
      <link>https://womenofwicca.nl/archive/hacking-hoomans/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2019 18:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://womenofwicca.nl/archive/hacking-hoomans/</guid>
      <description>Thu, Apr 25, 6:00 PM to 9:00 PM Location: Deloitte Amsterdam
 Humans are the weakest link in the information security chain. everyone in infosec
 This evening is hosted by Deloitte (thank you, Andrea!) and we will talk about all things physical security. Additionally, Deloitte will be providing food and drinks!
Are you a woman interested or working in security? Sign up!
This isn&amp;rsquo;t going to be a formal presentation but something more like a casual workshop where we share our fun social engineering experiences and talk about breaking into buildings.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Into the FireEye</title>
      <link>https://womenofwicca.nl/archive/fireeye/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2019 07:57:12 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://womenofwicca.nl/archive/fireeye/</guid>
      <description>Mon, Mar 25, 6:00 PM to 9:00 PM Location: Singel 236
Are you a woman working or interested in computer security? Sign up!
This time, FireEye is inviting the ladies of InfoSec and female security enthusiasts in The Netherlands for a casual get-together in Amsterdam.
FireEye will be hosting us at their office by Dam Square and is providing drinks and snacks.
The event is women-only and is meant to be a space where we can share, support, and learn with each other.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WICCA Drinks&amp;Stories</title>
      <link>https://womenofwicca.nl/archive/drinks-stories-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 20:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://womenofwicca.nl/archive/drinks-stories-1/</guid>
      <description>Fri, Feb 22, 8:00 PM to 10:00 PM Location: De Boterwaag
WICCA is coming to The Hague for some drinks and hacker stories. Are you a woman working or interested in computer security? Join us for some goofy hacker fun!
The event will start 20:00. We have reserved some space at Boterwaag on the Grote Markt.
Do you have an interesting hacker story to tell? Something that happened to you or some cool h4x0r shizzle you did?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Ladies of InfoSec</title>
      <link>https://womenofwicca.nl/archive/ladies-of-infosec/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jan 2019 18:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://womenofwicca.nl/archive/ladies-of-infosec/</guid>
      <description>Thu, Jan 31, 6:00 PM to 9:00 PM Location: KPN Teleport
Are you a woman working or interested in computer security? Sign up!
It&amp;rsquo;s time to kickoff the WICCA initiative with a casual get together, inviting the ladies of InfoSec and female security enthusiasts in The Netherlands to join us in Amsterdam. We will introduce ourselves and present on computer security-related topics, but most of all, make bad crypto jokes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://womenofwicca.nl/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://womenofwicca.nl/about/</guid>
      <description>What is WICCA? WICCA is a circle of women in cybersecurity based out in The Netherlands with a vision to spread the infosec word to everyone.
Our goal is to bring infosec ladies and female security enthusiasts together to learn about exploits, hacking, incident response, forensics, the low-level stuff, and especially make bad crypto jokes! We want to build a community of badass women in the Netherlands and hopefully inspire future generations to join keyboards and get the hacking started!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://womenofwicca.nl/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://womenofwicca.nl/contact/</guid>
      <description>How to get in touch with us Have questions or suggestions? Feel free to contact us at info@womenofwicca.nl.
We also have a WICCA mailing list to keep subscribers up-to-date with our events. If you wish to be added, just drop us a mail! 😄</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Donate to WICCA</title>
      <link>https://womenofwicca.nl/donate/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://womenofwicca.nl/donate/</guid>
      <description>WICCA currently does not accept any cash donations.
If you wish to still donate something to make our events even greater, it can be in terms of:
 Stickers (there&amp;rsquo;s never enough stickers!) T-shirts and other WICCA goodies Food and/or drinks for an event Tickets to a large event for our members &amp;hellip; more creative things!  You can contact donate@womenofwicca.nl, we will be highly grateful!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gallery</title>
      <link>https://womenofwicca.nl/gallery/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://womenofwicca.nl/gallery/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wick-Ed</title>
      <link>https://womenofwicca.nl/wick-ed/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://womenofwicca.nl/wick-ed/</guid>
      <description> Wick-Ed is the WICCA initiative to teach aspiring female security newcomers about computer security. Wick-Ed courses include recorded introductory lessons on offensive security, binary exploitation, and more to come. The Wick-Ed collection of recorded lessons can be found on YouTube.
Playlist  Offensive Security  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>