<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>WICCA</title>
    <link>https://womenofwicca.nl/</link>
    <description>Recent content on WICCA</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2019 18:00:00 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://womenofwicca.nl/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>WICCA Goes Hardwear!</title>
      <link>https://womenofwicca.nl/events/wicca-goes-hardwear/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2019 18:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://womenofwicca.nl/events/wicca-goes-hardwear/</guid>
      <description>Wed, Sep 25, 6:00 PM Location: Hotel NH Den Haag
Great news!!! The organisers of hardwear.io have invited us for a special women-only session on hardware security!
Hardwear.io is the biggest hardware security conference in Europe, and possibly in the world. It is a platform where researchers showcase and discuss their innovative research on attacking and defending hardware.
https://hardwear.io/netherlands-2019/
This session takes place during the hardwear.io week, right after the trainings and before the official conference starts, directly at the venue in The Hague WTC.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dutch Police: The Fight Against Cybercrime</title>
      <link>https://womenofwicca.nl/events/dutch-police/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Sep 2019 18:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://womenofwicca.nl/events/dutch-police/</guid>
      <description> Mon, Sep 23, 6:00 PM Location: Deloitte Amsterdam
WICCA is going awol to a session organised together with Team High Tech Crime and Team Digitale Opsporing, the Dutch police cyber units.
Deloitte will be hosting us all with food and drinks.
Are you a woman working or interested in security and cyber crime? Stay tuned!
Sign up on Meetup </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Secure Coding (... or the Art of Avoiding Data Breaches)</title>
      <link>https://womenofwicca.nl/archives/secure-coding/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2019 18:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://womenofwicca.nl/archives/secure-coding/</guid>
      <description>Fri, Aug 30, 6:00 PM to 9:00 PM Location: Saturnusstraat 14
WICCA is coming to The Hague for a session on secure coding and privacy-oriented software engineering. This session is organised together with Okuna and will cover the following topics: secure coding, privacy preservation, security and development.
Okuna (previously Openbook) embodies the future of social media: a privacy-oriented and transparent platform that is secure by design, which strives for a better tomorrow for our online social circles.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wick-Ed Offensive Security</title>
      <link>https://womenofwicca.nl/archives/wick-ed-offensive-security/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Jun 2019 18:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://womenofwicca.nl/archives/wick-ed-offensive-security/</guid>
      <description>Wick-Ed slides can be found here Lesson recording on YouTube Mon, Jul 29, 6:00 PM to 9:00 PM Location: KPN Teleport
WICCA kicks off a new initiative to teach ladies about security: Wick-Ed!
Because of the high Offensive Security training demand, we will be doing the first Wick-Ed session on Offensive Security on July 29. KPN will be hosting us again and is providing food and drinks. For anyone who could not attend the 2-day training on May 25-26, this is the occasion to pick up on the basics of offsec!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WICCA Drinks&amp;Stories</title>
      <link>https://womenofwicca.nl/archives/drinks-stories-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2019 10:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://womenofwicca.nl/archives/drinks-stories-2/</guid>
      <description>Thu, Jun 20, 8:00 PM to 10:00 PM Location: Pllek
WICCA is breaking into Amsterdam for some drinks and hacker stories. Are you a woman working or interested in computer security? Join us for some goofy hacker fun! Male +1s are welcome.
The event will start 20:00 and the place to be is: Pllek, which is reachable by (free) ferry from Amsterdam Centraal station.
Just a heads-up, every one should take care of their own consumption, as this is just a get-together event among fellow willing WICCA ladies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Offensive Security 101</title>
      <link>https://womenofwicca.nl/archives/offensive-security-101/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 May 2019 10:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://womenofwicca.nl/archives/offensive-security-101/</guid>
      <description>Training slides can be found here Sat, May 25, 10:00 AM to Sun, May 26, 5:00 PM Location: Securify
WICCA is giving a two-day training in Offensive Security especially for beginners. Securify is hosting us in their Sloterdijk office and will be providing lunch and Club Mate!
The training will include:
 Basic infrastructure and web introduction Network vulnerability scanning Offensive Security tooling Web application pwnage OWASP Top 10 Kernel exploits A tiny bit about malware reversing A Hackback CTF-like game Demos and more demos!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kubernetes with WICCA &amp; null Amsterdam @Adyen</title>
      <link>https://womenofwicca.nl/archives/kubernetes-wicca-null-adyen/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2019 18:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://womenofwicca.nl/archives/kubernetes-wicca-null-adyen/</guid>
      <description>Mon, May 13, 6:00 PM to 9:30 PM Location: Adyen
This evening session is a joint meetup between WICCA and null hosted by Adyen, where members from both communities are happily invited to attend. Adyen is a global payment service provider based in Amsterdam. They will be providing food and drinks for all of us!!! 😄
null is India&amp;rsquo;s largest open security community with chapters all over the world, including Amsterdam.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hacking Hoomans</title>
      <link>https://womenofwicca.nl/archives/hacking-hoomans/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2019 18:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://womenofwicca.nl/archives/hacking-hoomans/</guid>
      <description>Thu, Apr 25, 6:00 PM to 9:00 PM Location: Deloitte Amsterdam
 Humans are the weakest link in the information security chain. everyone in infosec
 This evening is hosted by Deloitte (thank you, Andrea!) and we will talk about all things physical security. Additionally, Deloitte will be providing food and drinks!
Are you a woman interested or working in security? Sign up!
This isn&amp;rsquo;t going to be a formal presentation but something more like a casual workshop where we share our fun social engineering experiences and talk about breaking into buildings.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Into the FireEye</title>
      <link>https://womenofwicca.nl/archives/fireeye/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2019 07:57:12 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://womenofwicca.nl/archives/fireeye/</guid>
      <description>Mon, Mar 25, 6:00 PM to 9:00 PM Location: Singel 236
Are you a woman working or interested in computer security? Sign up!
This time, FireEye is inviting the ladies of InfoSec and female security enthusiasts in The Netherlands for a casual get-together in Amsterdam.
FireEye will be hosting us at their office by Dam Square and is providing drinks and snacks.
The event is women-only and is meant to be a space where we can share, support, and learn with each other.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WICCA Drinks&amp;Stories</title>
      <link>https://womenofwicca.nl/archives/drinks-stories-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Feb 2019 20:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://womenofwicca.nl/archives/drinks-stories-1/</guid>
      <description>Fri, Feb 22, 8:00 PM to 10:00 PM Location: De Boterwaag
WICCA is coming to The Hague for some drinks and hacker stories. Are you a woman working or interested in computer security? Join us for some goofy hacker fun!
The event will start 20:00. We have reserved some space at Boterwaag on the Grote Markt.
Do you have an interesting hacker story to tell? Something that happened to you or some cool h4x0r shizzle you did?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Ladies of InfoSec</title>
      <link>https://womenofwicca.nl/archives/ladies-of-infosec/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jan 2019 18:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://womenofwicca.nl/archives/ladies-of-infosec/</guid>
      <description>Thu, Jan 31, 6:00 PM to 9:00 PM Location: KPN Teleport
Are you a woman working or interested in computer security? Sign up!
It&amp;rsquo;s time to kickoff the WICCA initiative with a casual get together, inviting the ladies of InfoSec and female security enthusiasts in The Netherlands to join us in Amsterdam. We will introduce ourselves and present on computer security-related topics, but most of all, make bad crypto jokes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://womenofwicca.nl/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://womenofwicca.nl/about/</guid>
      <description>What is WICCA? WICCA is a circle of women in cybersecurity based out in Amsterdam and surroundings with a vision to spread the infosec word to everyone.
Our goal is to bring infosec ladies and female security enthusiasts together to learn about exploits, hacking, incident response, forensics, the low-level stuff, and especially make bad crypto jokes! We want to build a community of badass women in the Netherlands and hopefully inspire future generations to join keyboards and get the hacking started!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://womenofwicca.nl/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://womenofwicca.nl/contact/</guid>
      <description>How to get in touch with us Have questions or suggestions? Feel free to contact us at info@womenofwicca.nl.
We also have a WICCA mailing list to keep subscribers up-to-date with our events. If you wish to be added, just drop us a mail! 😄</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Donate to WICCA</title>
      <link>https://womenofwicca.nl/donate/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://womenofwicca.nl/donate/</guid>
      <description> ETA soon&amp;hellip; </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>