<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>WICCA</title>
    <link>https://womenofwicca.nl/</link>
    <description>Recent content on WICCA</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2019 18:00:00 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://womenofwicca.nl/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>WICCA Goes Hardwear!</title>
      <link>https://womenofwicca.nl/events/wicca-goes-hardwear/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Sep 2019 18:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://womenofwicca.nl/events/wicca-goes-hardwear/</guid>
      <description>Wed, Sep 25, 6:00 PM Location: Hotel NH Den Haag Great news!!! The organisers of hardwear.io have invited us for a special women-only session on hardware security!
Hardwear.io is the biggest hardware security conference in Europe, and possibly in the world. It is a platform where researchers showcase and discuss their innovative research on attacking and defending hardware.
https://hardwear.io/netherlands-2019/
This session takes place during the hardwear.io week, right after the trainings and before the official conference starts, directly at the venue in The Hague WTC.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dutch Police: The Fight Against Cybercrime</title>
      <link>https://womenofwicca.nl/events/dutch-police/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Sep 2019 18:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://womenofwicca.nl/events/dutch-police/</guid>
      <description> Mon, Sep 23, 6:00 PM Location: Deloitte Amsterdam WICCA is going awol to a session organised together with Team High Tech Crime and Team Digitale Opsporing, the Dutch police cyber units.
Deloitte will be hosting us all with food and drinks.
Are you a woman working or interested in security and cyber crime? Stay tuned!
Sign up on Meetup </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://womenofwicca.nl/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://womenofwicca.nl/about/</guid>
      <description>What is WICCA? WICCA is a circle of women in cybersecurity based out in Amsterdam and surroundings with a vision to spread the infosec word to everyone.
Our goal is to bring infosec ladies and female security enthusiasts together to learn about exploits, hacking, incident response, forensics, the low-level stuff, and especially make bad crypto jokes! We want to build a community of badass women in the Netherlands and hopefully inspire future generations to join keyboards and get the hacking started!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://womenofwicca.nl/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://womenofwicca.nl/contact/</guid>
      <description>How to get in touch with us Have questions or suggestions? Feel free to contact us at info@womenofwicca.nl.
We also have a WICCA mailing list to keep subscribers up-to-date with our events. If you wish to be added, just drop us a mail! 😄</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>